Association of Canadian Publishers fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Subject files, 1951 - 1984; F-57-5; 4.91 m of textual records ca. 50 photographs; Physical description: 1 photograph located in F-57-5-1-3 Physical description: 26 photographs located in F-57-5-9-11
  Series consists of subject files of the ACP relating to its founding, finances, organizations, government departments, persons, topics, press releases and IPA administrative, policy, research and service functions.
  Included are correspondence and memoranda, reports and briefs, newsletters, articles, news clippings, press releases, minutes, budgets, grant applications and financial statements, survey responses, catalogues and photographs.
  - Founding, 1969 - 1972; F-57-5-1; 3 cm of textual records
    - Maynard Gertler, 1969 - 1970; F-57-5-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
    - Council of Canadian Publishers, 1970 - 1971; F-57-5-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
    - May Cutler - corresponcdence and photograph, 1970 - 1971; F-57-5-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
      Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Emergency Committee and IPA - Government Relations: Peter Martin, 1970 - 1972; F-57-5-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
  - Subject files, 1970 - 1974; F-57-5-2; 56 cm of textual records
    - Aid to Small Publishers: IPA, 1972; F-57-5-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
    - Alberta - government, 1973 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
    - Association for the Export of Canadian Books (AECB), 1972; F-57-5-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
    - Association for the Export of Canadian Books (AECB), 1973 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
    - Association for the Export of Canadian Books (AECB), 1972 - 1973; F-57-5-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
    - Association for the Export of Canadian Books (AECB) - contracts, proxies, correspondence, 1973; F-57-5-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
    - Association for the Export of Canadian Books (AECB), 1973 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
    - Association of Canadian University Teachers of English, 1972; F-57-5-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
    - Association of Canadian Community Colleges, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
    - Association of Canadian University Presses, 1972; F-57-5-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
    - Atlantic Publishers Association (A.P.A.), 1973; F-57-5-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
    - A.P.A. - Audley, Paul, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
    - A - Miscelleaneous Correspondence, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
    - Backlist Project, F-57-5-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
    - BACQUE, James: newpress, 1972 - 1973; F-57-5-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-25)
    - Book bus - promotion, clippings, photograph, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - Book, definition of, 1972; F-57-5-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - Book Market, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - Book Promotion and Information Centre, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - Books Canada - correspondence, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - Books Canada, U.K. (and Photographs), 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - Books for Native Children in Toronto, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - Books in Canada, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - Books in Print, F-57-5-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - Brampton Public Library, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - British Columbia Booksellers Association, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - B.C. Government, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - B.C. Publishers Group, 1973 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - Brochures Mailed - A-L, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - Brochures Mailed - M-Z, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - B - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1973 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - Cabinet memo to D. Godfrey, re. Gray Report, 1972; F-57-5-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - Canada Book Week, 1972; F-57-5-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - Canada Council - correspondence, 1971 - 1972; F-57-5-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 57-26)
    - Canada Council - Applications, 1972; F-57-5-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 57-27)
    - Canada Council - Budget, 1972; F-57-5-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 57-27)
    - Canada Council - News Releases, 1972; F-57-5-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 57-27)
    - Canada Council - Block Grants, 1972 - 1973; F-57-5-2-0-38 (Archival box - standard 57-27)
    - Canada Council - General, 1973; F-57-5-2-0-39 (Archival box - standard 57-27)
    - Canada Council - Budgets, 1973 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-40 (Archival box - standard 57-27)
    - Canada Council - General, 1973 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-41 (Archival box - standard 57-27)
    - Canada Council - Block Grants, 1973; F-57-5-2-0-42 (Archival box - standard 57-27)
    - Canada Council - Block Grants, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-43 (Archival box - standard 57-27)
    - Canada Council - Operating Grants, 1973 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-44 (Archival box - standard 57-27)
    - Canada Council - News Releases, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-45 (Archival box - standard 57-27)
    - Canada Studies Foundation, 1973; F-57-5-2-0-46 (Archival box - standard 57-27)
    - Canadian Authors Association, 1971 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-47 (Archival box - standard 57-27)
    - Canadian Book Design Committee, 1973 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-48 (Archival box - standard 57-27)
    - Canadian Book Design Committee, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-49 (Archival box - standard 57-27)
    - Canadian Book Publishers Council, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-50 (Archival box - standard 57-28)
    - Canadian Booksellers Association, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-51 (Archival box - standard 57-28)
    - Canadian Conference of the Arts, 1972 - 1973; F-57-5-2-0-52 (Archival box - standard 57-28)
    - Canadian Copyright Council, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-53 (Archival box - standard 57-28)
    - Canadian Library Association, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-54 (Archival box - standard 57-28)
    - Canadian National Exhibition, 1973 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-55 (Archival box - standard 57-28)
    - Canadian Periodical Publishers Association, 1973 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-56 (Archival box - standard 57-28)
    - Canadian Publishers Mailing Service, 1973; F-57-5-2-0-57 (Archival box - standard 57-28)
    - Canadian Radio and Telecommunications Commission, 1972; F-57-5-2-0-58 (Archival box - standard 57-28)
    - Canlit - Publishers Survey Research Group, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-59 (Archival box - standard 57-28)
    - Carriage Paid Pricing Ad-hoc Committee, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-60 (Archival box - standard 57-28)
    - Clark, Dr. William: correspondence, speech, 1973 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-61 (Archival box - standard 57-28)
    - College Biblio Centre Newsletter, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-62 (Archival box - standard 57-28)
    - Committee for Cross-Cultural Communication, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-63 (Archival box - standard 57-28)
    - Competition Act, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-64 (Archival box - standard 57-28)
    - Conference on Children's Literature, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-65 (Archival box - standard 57-28)
    - Conseil Superior du Livre, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-66 (Archival box - standard 57-28)
    - Copyright, 1971; F-57-5-2-0-67 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - Correspondence - Maynard Gertler, Peter Martin, Dave Godfrey, 1970 - 1973; F-57-5-2-0-68 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - John Coutts Library Service ltd., 1972 - 1973; F-57-5-2-0-69 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - May Cutler, President, Tundra, 1972; F-57-5-2-0-70 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - C - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-71 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - Davis, William - Correspondence, 1972; F-57-5-2-0-72 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - D - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-73 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - Edi-Quebec, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-74 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - Education, Departments of, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-75 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - Education Market Information, 1973; F-57-5-2-0-76 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - Educational Sales Consortium, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-77 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - Epogravure, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-78 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - Executive and Committees lists, 1973 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-79 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - External Affairs, Department of, 1974; F-57-5-2-0-80 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - E - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-81 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - Fairweather, Gordon, MP, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-2-0-82 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
  - Financial, 1971 - 1975; F-57-5-3; 23 cm of textual records
    - Accounts and correspondence, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - Budget and financial statements, 1971 - 1974; F-57-5-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - Financial survey proposed by Secretary of State, 1974; F-57-5-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - Foreign rights, 1972; F-57-5-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - Fort Frances Data Centre, 1972 - 1973; F-57-5-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - Frankfurt bookfair, 1972 - 1973; F-57-5-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - Frankfurt - correspondence and reports, 1974 - 1975; F-57-5-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - Frankfurt - publisher submissions, 1974; F-57-5-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-29)
    - Frankfurt - title fact sheets and master list, 1974; F-57-5-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - Friends of Egerton Ryerson demonstration, 1972; F-57-5-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - F - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1974; F-57-5-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - Globe and Mail - advertisement, 1973 - 1974; F-57-5-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - Globe and Mail - correspondence, 1974; F-57-5-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - Godfrey, David and Ellen: memos to / from T. Hartling, 1972 - 1973; F-57-5-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - Godfrey, David: unfiled correspondence, 1972; F-57-5-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - Grafferty, Howard, MP, 1974; F-57-5-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - Graphic Arts International Union, 1972; F-57-5-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - G - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - Hebert, Jacques, 1972; F-57-5-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - H - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1973 - 1974; F-57-5-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - IPA - Administration, 1973 - 1974; F-57-5-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - Industry, Trade and Commerce, Department of, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - Information Canada, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - International Book Year, 1972; F-57-5-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - International Publishers Association, 1972 - 1973; F-57-5-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - I - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - McClelland and Stewart, 1971 - 1972; F-57-5-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - Mailing Lists, 1974; F-57-5-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - Mailing List - IPA, 1974; F-57-5-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - Membership List, 1973; F-57-5-3-0-30 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - Memoranda, 1971 - 1973; F-57-5-3-0-31 (Archival box - standard 57-30)
    - Moratorium for Mass Paperback Rights Survey, 1974; F-57-5-3-0-32 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - Office and Employees, 1972 - 1974; F-57-5-3-0-33 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - Oromocto Canada Day, 1974; F-57-5-3-0-34 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - Policy, IPA Statements, 1972; F-57-5-3-0-35 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - President's Letter (missing nos. 6, 12, 21), 1974; F-57-5-3-0-36 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - President's Report, 1972; F-57-5-3-0-37 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - Press Conferences - Report on English Language Book Publishing, 1974; F-57-5-3-0-38 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - Press Releases, clippings, ads, 1973; F-57-5-3-0-39 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - Royal Commission on Book Publishing - IPA, CBPC Briefs, Order in Council, 1971; F-57-5-3-0-40 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - Small Presses Conference, 1974; F-57-5-3-0-41 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - Social Science and Humanities Research Council, 1972; F-57-5-3-0-42 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - Unesco, Seminar on Cultural Policies, 1972; F-57-5-3-0-43 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
  - General files, 1973 - 1976; F-57-5-4; 42 cm of textual records
    - Alberta Publishers Association, 1974 - 1975; F-57-5-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - A - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - Belford Books Distributing Co, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - Book Promotion and Information Centre, 1974 - 1975; F-57-5-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - Books Canada - A.E.C.B., 1975; F-57-5-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - Bookstore Promotion - Labels, Correspondence, 1974 - 1975; F-57-5-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - British Columbia Publishers Group, 1974 - 1975; F-57-5-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - Brochure and Information Requests, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - B - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - Canada Council, 1974 - 1975; F-57-5-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-31)
    - Canadian Backlist Project, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Canadian Book Promotion Centre, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Canadian Book Packages for Libraries, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Canadian Book Publishers Association, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Canadian Books in Print, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Canadian Booksellers Association, 1974 - 1975; F-57-5-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Canadian Communications Research Info Centre - Newsletter, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Canadian Library Association, 1974 - 1975; F-57-5-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Canadian Periodical Publishers Association, 1974 - 1975; F-57-5-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Canadian Publishers Project Co-ordinating Committee, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Cataloguing in Publication - survey, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Commonwealth Poetry Prize Convention Facilities, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Convention Facilities, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-23 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Copyright, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-24 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - C - Miscellaneous, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-25 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Display Program, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-26 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - D - Miscellaneous, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-27 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Edi-Quebec, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-28 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Edmonton Journal, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-29 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Education, Boards of - Purchase orders for books, Longhouse, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-30 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Education, 1973 - 1975; F-57-5-4-0-31 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Executive and Committees, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-32 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Exports - Federal Subcommittee, 1973 - 1975; F-57-5-4-0-33 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - E - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-34 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Farguson, Roger: Self-Counsel Press, 1974 - 1975; F-57-5-4-0-35 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Federation of Women's Teachers Association of Ontario, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-36 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Financial, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-37 (Archival box - standard 57-32)
    - Frankfurt International Book Fair, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-38 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - Frankfurt Fair - correspondence, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-39 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - Frankfurt Fair - publishers submissions, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-40 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - Frankfurt - reports, 1976; F-57-5-4-0-41 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - Frankfurt - title sheets, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-42 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - F - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-43 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - Globe and Mail, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-44 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - G and H - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-45 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - International Publishers Association, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-46 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - I, J, K - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-47 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - Library Information Services, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-48 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - Literary Presses Group, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-49 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - L - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-50 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - McClelland and Stewart, 1974 - 1975; F-57-5-4-0-51 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - McIntyre, Scott, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-52 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - MacMillan Co. of Canada, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-53 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - Mailing Services: Division of General Publishing Co. Ltd., 1975; F-57-5-4-0-54 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - Media - '75 Conference, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-55 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - Media - Advertising, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-56 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - Membership - memoranda to, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-57 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - Montreal International Book Fair - reports and correspondence, 1974 - 1975; F-57-5-4-0-58 (Archival box - standard 57-33)
    - Montreal International Book Fair - Correspondence, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-59 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - Montreal International Book Fair - Papers re sale of rights, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-60 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - Montreal International Book Fair - reports, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-61 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - M - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-62 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - National Library of Canada, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-62 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - Office and Employees file list, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-63 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - Ontario Development Corporation, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-63 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - Ontario, Government of - Education, Colleges and Universities, Culture and Recreation, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-64 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - Ottawa Journal, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-65 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - O - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-66 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - Postal Strike, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-67 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - Press Releases, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-68 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - P, Q, R - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-69 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - Secretary of State - Hugh Faulkner, MP, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-70 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - Speaker's Bureau, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-71 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - Speeches and Reports, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-72 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - S - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-73 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - Toronto Star, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-74 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - T - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-75 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - Unesco, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-76 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - U - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-78 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - Wholesaling Crisis, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-79 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - Writers Union of Canada, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-80 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - W, X, Y, Z - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975; F-57-5-4-0-81 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
  - General files, 1974 - 1977; F-57-5-5; 27 cm of textual records
    - Alberta Publishers Association, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - American Library Association, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - Anti-Trust Suit (US), 1976; F-57-5-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - Atlantic Publishers Association, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - B.C. Publishers Group - briefs, 1974 - 1976; F-57-5-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - B.C. Publishers Group - Minutes and Papers, 1975 - 1976; F-57-5-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-34)
    - B.C. Publishers Group, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-35)
    - B.C. Publishers Group, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-35)
    - Buyers Guide to Canadian Titles (ACP), 1976; F-57-5-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-35)
    - Canada Council - Correspondence, 1975 - 1976; F-57-5-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-35)
    - Canada Council - Operating Grants, 1975 - 1976; F-57-5-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-35)
    - Canadian Booksellers Association, 1975 - 1976; F-57-5-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-35)
    - Canadian Childrens Book Centre, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-35)
    - Canadian Publishing Conference, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-35)
    - Copyright Literature, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-5-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-35)
    - English Language Publishing Statistics: A Response, H. Bohne, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-35)
    - Executive and Committees, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-35)
    - Frankfurt Book Fair, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-35)
    - Library Survey - by IPA, re. Canadian Holdings, 1974 - 1976; F-57-5-5-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-35)
    - Library Survey - research materials, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-36)
    - Membership correspondence, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-36)
    - Members Handbook (ACP), 1976; F-57-5-5-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-36)
    - Money side of Publishing (article Association of American Publishers), 1976; F-57-5-5-0-23 (Archival box - standard 57-36)
    - Montreal International Book Fair, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-24 (Archival box - standard 57-36)
    - Montreal International Book Fair - Fact Sheets, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-25 (Archival box - standard 57-36)
    - Montreal International Book Fair - Publishers Stands, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-26 (Archival box - standard 57-36)
    - Music Publishers Group, 1974 - 1976; F-57-5-5-0-27 (Archival box - standard 57-36)
    - Office, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-28 (Archival box - standard 57-36)
    - Oromocto Book Prize, 1975 - 1976; F-57-5-5-0-29 (Archival box - standard 57-36)
    - Ontario Arts Council - summer student employment, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-30 (Archival box - standard 57-36)
    - Requests for Information, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-5-0-31 (Archival box - standard 57-36)
    - Subscriptions, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-32 (Archival box - standard 57-36)
    - Teachers and Writers Education Project, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-33 (Archival box - standard 57-36)
    - Warsaw Book Fair, 1976; F-57-5-5-0-34 (Archival box - standard 57-36)
  - General files, 1975 - 1978; F-57-5-6; 35 cm of textual records